{
    "subject": "resource/MediaCoder",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "MediaCoder",
    "human_readable": "MediaCoder's name is MediaCoder.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9693095088005066,
            "question": "What is the name of MediaCoder?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8494714498519897,
            "question": "What are some features of MediaCoder?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8470718860626221,
            "question": "Who developed MediaCoder?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6468714475631714,
            "question": "Is MediaCoder a software application?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5543763041496277,
            "question": "Is MediaCoder open-source software?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5527195334434509,
            "question": "What are some alternatives to MediaCoder?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5217435359954834,
            "question": "How is MediaCoder used in media production?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5039913654327393,
            "question": "Where can users download MediaCoder?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44126859307289124,
            "question": "Does MediaCoder support batch processing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44082969427108765,
            "question": "What types of media files can MediaCoder handle?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=MediaCoder's name is MediaCoder.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1255_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does MediaCoder support batch processing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1255_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can users download MediaCoder?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1255_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is MediaCoder used in media production?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1255_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1255_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1255_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1255_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1255_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1255_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1255_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1255_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1255_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1255_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1255_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents consistently refer to the software as \"MediaCoder\", with no variations or alternative names mentioned. Therefore, it can be concluded that the statement \"MediaCoder's name is MediaCoder\" is supported by the context information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}